<resources>
    <!-- General information -->
    <string name="organization_name">TeoG</string>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Swift</string>

    <!-- Information Texts -->
    <string name="menu_information">information</string>
    <string name="newdevice_activity_1">Please put a fresh barcode sticker on the device you want to register and scan it with your camera.</string>
    <string name="newdevice_activity_2">Please enter all general data known about the device.</string>
    <string name="newdevice_activity_3">Please take a snapshot of the device, so your colleagues can indentify it easily.</string>
    <string name="reportcreation_activity">Please add a short description about what problems the device has and what you have done in order to solve them.</string>
    <string name="userinfo_activity">You can use this data to contact your colleagues or staff at other hospitals.</string>
    <string name="userprofile_activity">This is your very own user profile. You can add some general information like your telephone number and position here.</string>
    <string name="mainactivity"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Barcode Scanner</b><br>
        The Scanner tab lets you scan registered barcodes and leads you directly to the respective device page. Alternatively you can enter the number of the ID sticker, if scanning is not possible.</p>
        <p><b>TODO List</b><br>
        The TODO tab gives you an overview of all devices that are broken or up for maintenance. If a colleague is already working on a case, it will be displayed as <i>in progress</i>.</p>
        <p><b>Calendar</b><br>
        The calendar will provide you an overview of the next upcoming maintenance activities.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="privacy_policy"><![CDATA[
    <h2>Privacy Policy</h2>
    <p>Personal data (usually referred to just as "data" below) will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for the purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly app, including its contents, and the services offered.</p>
    <p>Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the "GDPR"), "processing" refers to any operation or set of operations such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available, alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.</p>
    <p>The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis for the processing of such data either under our own control or in conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve the user experience which may result in said third parties also processing data they collect and control.</p>
    <p>Our privacy policy is structured as follows:</p>
    <p>I. Information about us as controllers of your data<br>II. The rights of users and data subjects<br>III. Information about the data processing</p>
    <h3>I. Information about us as controllers of your data</h3>
    <p>The party responsible for this app (the "controller") for purposes of data protection law is:</p>
    <p><span style="color: #ff0000;">Technik ohne Grenzen e.V.</span><br><span style="color: #ff0000;">Richard-Strauß-Straße 38</span><br><span style="color: #ff0000;">91315 Höchstadt</span><br><span style="color: #ff0000;">Germany</span></p>
    <p><span style="color: #ff0000;"><span style="color: #ff0000;">Email: datenschutz@teog.de</span></p>
    <h3>II. The rights of users and data subjects</h3>
    <p>With regard to the data processing to be described in more detail below, users and data subjects have the right</p>
    <ul type="disc">
    <li>to confirmation of whether data concerning them is being processed, information about the data being processed, further information about the nature of the data processing, and copies of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);</li>
    <li>to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf. also Art. 16 GDPR);</li>
    <li>to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said processing per Art. 18 GDPR;</li>
    <li>to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);</li>
    <li>to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they believe that data concerning them is being processed by the controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art. 77 GDPR).</li>
    </ul>
    <p>In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections, deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art. 16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these recipients.</p>
    <p><strong>Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have the right to object to the controller&apos;s future processing of their data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising is permissible.</strong></p>
    <h3>III. Information about the data processing</h3>
    <p>Your data processed when using our app will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.</p>

    <h4>Data storage and sharing</h4>
    <p>All of your data will be stored on a server run by our hosting provider <i>WebNet Service</i>. Apart from this technical necessity, no third parties are involved in the processing of your data.</p>

    <h4>Server access data</h4>
    <p>For technical reasons and to ensure a secure and stable app experience, the method and time the app running on your Android device accesses our server interface is stored in log files as well as the IP address of your device.</p>
    <p>The data thus collected will be temporarily stored, but not in association with any other of your data.</p>
    <p>The basis for this storage is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the improvement, stability, functionality, and security of our app.</p>

    <h4>Customer account/registration</h4>
    <p>If you create a customer account with us via email or our website, we will use the data you entered during registration (your name and your email address) exclusively for providing you permanent access to the app content.</p>
    <p>During the registration process, your consent will be obtained for this processing of your data, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected by us will be used exclusively to provide your customer account.</p>
    <p>If you give your consent to this processing, Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR is the legal basis for this processing.</p>
    <p>If the opening of the customer account is also intended to lead to the initiation of a contractual relationship with us or to fulfill an existing contract with us, the legal basis for this processing is also Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.</p>
    <p>You may revoke your prior consent to the processing of your personal data at any time under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent.</p>
    <p>The data previously collected will then be deleted as soon as processing is no longer necessary. However, we must observe any retention periods required under tax and commercial law.</p>

    <h4>Contact</h4>
    <p>If you contact us via email or the contact form, the data you provide will be used for the purpose of processing your request. We must have this data in order to process and answer your inquiry; otherwise we will not be able to answer it in full or at all.</p>
    <p>The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.</p>
    <p>Your data will be deleted once we have fully answered your inquiry and there is no further legal obligation to store your data, such as if an order or contract resulted therefrom.</p>

    <h4>User posts and comments</h4>
    <p>Our app offers you the opportunity to post work reports. If you make use of this feature, we will process your report, the date and time you submitted it, and your name and make it accessible to other app users.</p>
    <p>The legal basis for this is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR. You may revoke your prior consent under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent.</p>
    <p>All of the reports you write are linked to your personal account because we might have a legitimate interest in taking or supporting further action if your report infringes the rights of third parties and/or is otherwise unlawful.</p>
    <p>In this case, the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in any legal defense we may have to mount.</p>

    <p>Based on: <a href="https://www.ratgeberrecht.eu/leistungen/muster-datenschutzerklaerung.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Model Data Protection Statement</a> for <a href="https://www.ratgeberrecht.eu/" target="_blank">Anwaltskanzlei Weiß &amp; Partner</a></p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="about_text"><![CDATA[
        <h3>About TeoG Swift</h3>
        <p>TeoG Swift is an inventory and maintenance application, developed by the NGO Technik ohne Grenzen e.V. (Technology without borders). Its intended use is to establish a central database of hospital devices in a certain area, in order to document their repairs and simplify the search for spare parts.</p>
        ]]></string>

    <string name="teog_info"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Technology without Borders</b><br>
        WG Hospital Support</p>

        Contact:<br>
        hs@teog.de
        ]]></string>

    <!-- Activity names -->
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_device">Scan barcode</string>
    <string name="title_activity_device_info">Device info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_info">User info</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About Swift</string>

    <!-- Device states -->
    <string-array name="device_states">
        <item>working</item>
        <item>maintenance due</item>
        <item>repair needed</item>
        <item>in progress</item>
        <item>broken/salvage</item>
        <item>limited use</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="countries_options">
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Ghana</item>
        <item>Nepal</item>
        <item>Test</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="months">Months</string>
    <plurals name="months_count">
        <item quantity="one">%d Month</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d Months</item>
    </plurals>

    <!-- Miscellaneous Actions -->
    <string name="edit">edit</string>
    <string name="refresh">refresh</string>
    <string name="share">share</string>
    <string name="share_link">share link</string>
    <string name="want_to_show">I want to show you this %s: %s%s/%s/%d/</string>
    <string name="create">create</string>
    <string name="about">about</string>
    <string name="log_out">log out</string>
    <string name="licenses">licenses</string>
    <string name="my_profile">my profile</string>
    <string name="my_hospital">my hospital</string>
    <string name="user_management">User Management</string>
    <string name="import_export">Import/Export</string>

    <!-- Hospital Overview -->
    <string name="hospital_location_symbol">hospital location symbol</string>
    <string name="hospital_members_heading">Members</string>
    <string name="hospital_devices_heading">Devices</string>

    <!-- Info Dialog Texts -->
    <string name="info_dialog_heading">Information</string>
    <string name="info_dialog_confirmation">Got it!</string>

    <!-- Button/Image Placeholders -->
    <string name="edit_button_desc">edit button</string>
    <string name="teog_logo">TeoG logo</string>
    <string name="app_logo">app logo</string>
    <string name="next_button">next</string>
    <string name="take_picture_button">take picture</string>
    <string name="save_button">save</string>
    <string name="search_button">search</string>
    <string name="new_device_button">new device</string>
    <string name="create_report_button">create report</string>
    <string name="phone_symbol">call</string>
    <string name="mail_symbol">write mail</string>
    <string name="captured_image">captured image</string>
    <string name="device_state_icon">device state</string>
    <string name="previous_state">previous state</string>
    <string name="current_state">current state</string>
    <string name="toggle_light">toggle camera light</string>

    <!-- Login Screen -->
    <string name="login_button_text">Login</string>
    <string name="login_country_hint">Country</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="reset_pw_mail_missing">Please enter your e-mail address first</string>
    <string name="reset_pw">Reset password</string>
    <string name="forgot_pw_hint">Forgot your password?\nPlease select your country, enter your e-mail address and tap this text.</string>
    <string name="reset_pw_hint">Do you want to reset your password?\nA new one will be sent to:\n</string>

    <!-- Device Information -->
    <string name="device">Device</string>
    <string name="device_id">Device ID</string>
    <string name="device_image_placeholder">device image</string>
    <string name="device_asset_number">Asset Number</string>
    <string name="device_type">Type</string>
    <string name="device_model">Model</string>
    <string name="device_manufacturer">Manufacturer</string>
    <string name="device_serial_number">Serial Number</string>
    <string name="device_location">Location</string>
    <string name="device_maintenance_interval">Maint. Interval</string>
    <string name="device_recent_reports">Recent Reports</string>
    <string name="documents_overview">Available Documents</string>
    <string name="device_info_tutorial_attribute_table">This table lists all relevant data of a device.</string>
    <string name="device_info_tutorial_state_section">The current state of the device is shown up here.</string>
    <string name="device_info_tutorial_report_list">You can see the recent maintenance/repair history in the bottom section.</string>
    <string name="device_info_tutorial_report_creation">Use this button to create a new report.</string>
    <string name="device_info_tutorial_documents">If available, related documents can be retrieved by tapping this button.</string>

    <!-- Report Information -->
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="report_description">Description</string>
    <string name="report_info">Information</string>
    <string name="report_date">Date</string>
    <string name="report_state_change">State Change</string>
    <string name="report_author">Author</string>
    <string name="report_author_name" translatable="false">%s:</string>
    <string name="report_title">Title</string>
    <string name="report_description_description">please provide a description of what you have done</string>
    <string name="report_no_description">no description available</string>
    <string name="report_creation_invalid_state">new state can not match old state</string>
    <string name="report_tutorial_state_change">This section shows you the change of state the device went through in the selected report.</string>
    <string name="report_tutorial_description">The description contains all the information the creator of the report deemed to be important.</string>

    <!-- User Information -->
    <string name="user">User</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="user_telephone">Telephone</string>
    <string name="user_mail">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="user_position">Position</string>
    <string name="tap_to_call">tap to call\n%s</string>
    <string name="tap_to_mail">tap to mail\n%s</string>

    <!-- User Management -->
    <string name="create_user">Create new user</string>
    <string name="create_user_mail_hint">The user will receive his/her password via mail.</string>

    <!-- Hospital Information -->
    <string name="hospital">Hospital</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="filter">filter…</string>
    <string name="hospital_info_tutorial_state_overview">These symbols give you a quick overview over the states of your devices.</string>
    <string name="hospital_info_tutorial_asset_list">You can browse through a list of your colleagues or devices by expanding the respective section.</string>
    <string name="hospital_info_tutorial_filter">Use this field for filtering.</string>
    <plurals name="hospital_info_overdue_devices">
        <item quantity="one"> %d device is scheduled for maintenance</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d devices are scheduled for maintenance</item>
    </plurals>

    <!-- Main -->
    <string-array name="main_tab_names">
        <item>Scanner</item>
        <item>Todo</item>
        <item>Calendar</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Calendar -->
    <string name="days_left">days left</string>
    <string name="days_over">days over</string>
    <string name="devices_up_for_maintenance">Devices up for maintenance</string>

    <!-- User profile -->
    <string name="user_profile_tutorial_attribute_table">This table shows all of your user data.</string>
    <string name="user_profile_tutorial_edit">Tap the pencil symbols in order to change your information.</string>
    <string name="edit_mail_address_warning">You will need to remember your new mail address in order to log in.</string>

    <!-- Portation -->
    <string name="portation_export">Export</string>
    <string name="database_as_csv">Database as CSV</string>

    <!-- Error Messages -->
    <string name="generic_error_message">something went wrong</string>
    <string name="error_internet_connection">no internet connection</string>
    <string name="error_empty_mail">mail address is empty</string>
    <string name="error_empty_password">password is empty</string>
    <string name="empty_model">model is empty</string>
    <string name="empty_manufacturer">manufacturer is empty</string>
    <string name="empty_type">type is empty</string>
    <string name="empty_name">name is empty</string>
    <string name="empty_title">please add a title</string>
    <string name="server_comm_error_message">server communication problems</string>
    <string name="file_not_found">file not found</string>
    <string name="device_number_invalid">invalid device number</string>
    <string name="no_picture_attached">no picture attached</string>
    <string name="device_not_found">device not found</string>
    <string name="invalid_item_link">invalid item link</string>
    <string name="asset_wrong_hospital">asset is from a different hospital</string>
    <string name="asset_wrong_country">asset is from a different country</string>

    <!-- Dialog Texts -->
    <string name="dialog_cancel_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="dialog_ok_text">OK</string>

    <string name="initial_report_text">device creation</string>

    <string name="image_download_hint">tap icon to download image</string>

    <string name="e_mail_sent">E-mail has been sent</string>
    <string name="user_created">User has been created</string>

    <!-- Symbols -->
    <string name="line_break">%s\n%s</string>

</resources>